Guide to the Frank and Anne Warner Papers, 1899-2000 and undated, bulk 1933-1985 RL.01345
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Audiovisual Materials Series, circa 1920-2000 and undated, 14 boxes
  - Sound Recordings
    - Cassette Tapes (WC-1 to WC-59) (Box 22 (WC-1 to WC-17) and Box 23 (WC-18 to WC-32))
      - WC1 - WC32: Library of Congress listening copies (L of C Tapes 1 of 31 - L of C Tapes 31 of 31).
        - There is a one-to-one correspondence between the Library of Congress Masters ( reels) and the Library of Congress Copies ( cassette tapes) until cassette 15. Here, the correspondence becomes divergent with cassette tape WC-14 (L of C Tapes 14 of 31 #1) and WC-15 (L of C Tapes 14 of 31 #2). Listening copies from 15 through 32 are numbered accordingly with a WC number one unit greater than the L of C Tapes number, for example, WC-16 (L of C Tapes 15 of 31). (Box 22 (WC-1 to WC-17) and Box 23 (WC-18 to WC-32))
      - WC-33 - WC-35: Steve Wadsworth: Interview and Songs (Box 24)
      - WC-36 - WC-42: Unique Tapes
        - WC-36: Frank Warner, Songs of the Erie Canal, undated (Box 24)
        - WC-37: Frank Proffitt and Frank Proffitt, Jr., Vilas, N.C.: 1965 (Box 24)
        - WC-38: Frank Warner and family. Listen to America. (1975: Folktracks Recordings, FSV-901) [currently missing] (Box 24)
        - WC-39: Helen Kennedy Memorial Folk Concert. ( Cecil Sharp House: 1976 June 19) [currently missing] (Box 24)
        - WC-40: Gerret Warner Interviews Frank Warner on Run of the Arrow. (1976 Dec. 4) [currently missing] (Box 24)
        - WC-41 and WC-42: Frank Warner Memorial Concert. Two items. (1978 Dec. 2) (Box 24)
      - WC-43 - WC-59: Miscellaneous Cassette Tapes
        - WC-43: An unrehearsed evening with Carl Sandburg at the Warners' apartment at 144 W. 12th Street, New York City, N.Y. Present: Carl Sandburg, Frank and Anne Warner, Mari Jinishian, and Jean Ritchie, and Gregory d'Allessio. Includes conversation, vending cries, stories, songs, etc. (Autumn 1950). (Box 24)
        - WC-44: Tape sent to the Warners in September of 1974 by Buna Hicks; recorded on Beech Mountain, N.C., by Buna Hicks (Box 24)
        - WC-45: The Warners interveiw Charles Horace Fish (son of Lena Bourne Fish), Temple, N.H. (1976 Aug. 18) (Box 24)
        - WC-46: A visit with Buna Hicks in 1971 of Beech Mountain, N.C. Present: Frank, Anne, Jeff, and Susan Warner; Frank Proffitt, Jr.; and Buna Hicks. Side B: Four songs by Yankee John Galusha from 1941 (Box 24)
        - WC-47: Interview with Cliff and Marie Tillett, Wanchese, N.C. (1971 Feb.). Side B: Dick Tillett sings ten songs (1971) (Box 24)
        - WC-48: Frank, Jeff, and Gerret Warner perform at the Evening Program for the Seminars in American Culture, Cooperstown, N.Y. (1969 July 10) (Box 24)
        - WC-49: Frank Warner: Uncle Remus Stories (circa 1975): A: Squirrels, Specie, and The Lion. B: Heyo House and Terrifying Racket (Box 24)
        - WC-50: A Tribute to Frank Warner, Lee Knight program, S.C. Educational Radio. Program I, broadast 1978 Apr. 15; program II, broadcast 1978 Apr. 22 (Box 24)
        - WC-51: A Frank Warner Concert, 1 of 2: Concert at Elizabethtown School Auditorium, Elizabethtowm, N.Y. (1973 Apr. 21). Recorded by Lee Knight (Box 24)
        - WC-52: Frank Warner Concert, 2 of 2: Concert at Elizabethtown School Auditorium, Elizabethtown, N.Y. (1973 Apr. 21). Recorded by Lee Knight (Box 25)
        - WC-53: Frank Warner, Guitar Workshop Concert at My Father's Place, Roslyn, N.Y. (1972 Feb. 6). 1 of 2 (Box 25)
        - WC-54: Frank Warner, Guitar Workshop Concert at My Father's Place, Roslyn, N.Y. (1972 Feb. 6). 2 of 2 (Box 25)
        - WC-55: Billy Fair interviews Frank and Anne Warner for WBAI radio; memories of collecting (1962). 1 of 2 (Box 25)
        - WC-56: Billy Fair interviews Frank and Anne Warner for WBAI radio; memories of collecting (1962). 2 of 2 (Box 25)
        - WC-57: Warner Recollections: Frank, Anne, Gerret, and Jeff Warner; interviewer is Gerret Warner (1971 Dec. 27). 1 of 3 (Box 25)
        - WC-58: Warner Recollections: Frank, Anne, Gerret, and Jeff Warner; interviewer is Gerret Warner (1971 Dec. 27). 2 of 3 (Box 25)
        - WC-59: Warner Recollections: Frank, Anne, Gerret, and Jeff Warner; interviewer is Gerret Warner (1971 Dec. 27). 3 of 3 (Box 25)
    - Phonograph albums (Box 26)
      - American Traditional Folk Songs by Frank Warner. Reissue of Elektra 153. EKS-7153. 1 disc. 12 in. (Box 26)
      - The Civil War Through Its Songs and Ballads. With Frank Warner, Bill Bonyun and Others. Heirloom Records HL 503. 1961. 1 disc with notes. 12 in. (Box 26)
      - Come All You Good People. Frank Warner; with Jeff and Gerret Warner. Minstrel JD 204. 1979. 1 disc. 12 in. (Box 26)
      - Darlin' Sportin' Jenny / Theme from 'La Fayette' - Slowly, Slowly. The Brothers Four. Columbia 4-42391. 1 disc. 7 in. (Box 26)
      - The Folk Music of the Newport Folk Festival: Volume 2: 1959-60. Folkways Records FA 2432. 1961. 1 disc with notes. 12 in. (Box 26)
      - Frank Proffitt Sings Folk Songs. Recorded by Sandy Paton; edited by Frank Warner. Folkways Records FA 2360. 1962. 1 disc with notes. 12 in. (Box 26)
      - Frank Warner Sings American Folk Songs and Ballads. Elektra EKL3. 1952. 1 disc. 10 in. (Box 26)
      - Hudson Valley Songs. Disc Company of America 611 (5022-5024). 3 discs. 10 in. (Box 26)
      - I'm on My Way / Whiskey in the Jar. The Highwaymen. United Artists UA 439. 1 disc. 7 in. (Box 26)
      - Our Singing Heritage: Volume 3: Folk Songs Collected and Sung by Frank Warner. Additional Accompaniments by Billy Faier. Elektra 153. 1958. 1 disc. 12 in. (Box 26)
      - Songs and Ballads of America's Wars: From the French and Indian War to the Civil War. Sung by Frank Warner. Elektra EKL13. 1954. 1 disc. 10 in. (Box 26)
      - Songs of the Civil War, North and South. Sung by Frank Warner; with Jeff and Gerret Warner. Prestige International 13012. 1 disc. 12 in. (Box 26)
      - A Treasury of Folk Songs for Children, with 'Color me' Pictures Inside. Elektra EKL-223. 2 discs. 12 in. (Box 26)
    - Compact Discs (CDs)
      - Her Bright Smile Haunts Me Still: The Warner Collection, Volume 1. Appleseed Recordings (11587-1035-2), 2000 (Box 27)
      - Nothing Seems Better to Me: The Music of Frank Proffitt and NC. The Warner Collection, Volume II. Appleseed Recordings (11587-1035-2), 2000 (Box 27)
      - Jolly Tinker, Jeff Warner. Gumstump Records 101 (83707-18830), 2005 (Box 27)
  - Moving Images
    - Frank Warner home movies, 1920s, 1930s; Total running time 00:29:49
      Scope and Contents
      Footage of Greensboro and Durham, NC, coastal region, and New York City.
      - 16mm original (Box 32, Film-reel RL01345-F16-0002)
      - VHS copy (Box 27, Video-cassette RL01345-VHS-0001)
      - Digital preservation file scanned from 16mm original (Digital-materials RL01345-SET-0001, Video-file RL01345-F16-0002.mov)
    - Sea Songs, Lyrics and Legends Series, National Educational Television, 1963; 00:29:22
      Produced and directed by John Twaddle. Performers include: E. G. Huntington, Sam Eskin, Frank Warner, Phillip Merrill, Anne Warner, Jeff Warner, and Gerret Warner, and others. Shot at Old Mystic Seaport, Mystic, Connecticut. Part of the 15-episode Lyrics and Legends series produced by WHYY-TV for National Educational Television in 1963.
      - Umatic original (Box 27, Video-cassette RL01345-UM-0003)
      - Digital preservation file scanned from Umatic original (Digital-materials RL01345-SET-0001, Video-file RL01345-UM-0003.MOV)
    - Frank Proffitt at Newport. Introduction by Pete Seeger, 1963 July
      - 16mm original (Box 32, Film-reel RL01345-F16-0001)
      - Digital preservation file scanned from 16mm original (Digital-materials RL01345-SET-0001, Video-file RL01345-F16-0001.mov)
    - Rainbow Quest with Pete Seeger, episode 26, guest Frank Warner, 1966; 00:52:58
      This episode of Seeger's Rainbow Quest can be viewed on Youtube: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Pc7r6ZTR9E0 (March 2018).
      - Umatic original (Box 27, Video-cassette RL01345-UM-0001)
      - Digital preservation file scanned from Umatic original (Digital-materials RL01345-SET-0001, Video-file RL01345-UM-0001.MOV)
    - Frank Warner singing "Blue Mountain Lake", 1974
      Footage of logging with Frank Warner singing "Blue Mountain Lake" on the soundtrack. Used in an exhibit at the Adirondack Museum at Blue Mountain Lake, New York, in 1974.
      - Super 8mm original (Box 21, Film-reel RL01345-FS8-0001)
      - Digital preservation file scanned from Super 8mm original (Digital-materials RL01345-SET-0001, Video-file RL01345-FS8-0001.mov)
    - Music of Frank Warner. WLIW/Channel 21, circa 1971; 00:28:27
      Frank Warner speaks to young people at his home near Old Brookville, Nassau County, New York, about his experiences collecting folksongs. With Anne, Jeff and Gerret Warner, Long Island, New York. Note that the 16mm film copy is A and B roll rather than a composite, and the soundtrack appears incomplete. The Umatic video cassette and the digital file scanned from it contain the entire program.
      - 16mm original, bw, magnetic sound, "A" roll (Box 32, Film-reel RL01345-F16-0003)
      - 16mm original, bw, magnetic sound, "B" roll (Box 32, Film-reel RL01345-F16-0004)
      - Umatic original (Box 27, Video-cassette RL01345-UM-0002)
      - Digital preservation file scanned from Umatic original (Digital-materials RL01345-SET-0001, Video-file RL01345-UM-0002.MOV)
- Prints and Negatives Series, 1933-1969, 2 boxes
  Contains 239 black and white 4x5 prints, which are arranged alpha-numerically into lots from Lot 1 through Lot 9E. Within the lots, the prints are identified by number, for example, Lot 2A: 1, Lot 2A: 2. Through the photographs, the Warners captured images of many traditional American folk musicians and singers and often their families and homes as well. The Warners themselves appear frequently throughout the collection. There are several photographs in which Frank Warner is pictured playing and singing along with various musicians, among them: Nathan, Roby Monroe, Buna Vista, Ray, and Linzy Hicks and their families; Frank Proffitt; Yankee John Galusha; Lena Bourne Fish; the Tillett family; Louis Solomon and others from the Mohawk tribe at the St. Regis reservation (N.Y.); and Carl Sandburg. There are also interesting images that capture the Warners engaged in recording these sessions. The photographic documentation of the Warners' travels contains images from as far North as Vermont, as far East as the Outer Banks, N.C., and as far West as the western edge of North Carolina.
  - Prints Subseries, 1933-1969
    - Lot 1: 1933
      - 1A (1) Nag's Head, N.C.
        - Sue Thomas and Frank Warner. (Box 28, Print 1A: 1)
    - Lot 2, 1938
      - 2A (6) County Sing, Boone, N.C.
        - Nathan Hicks; Lewis Hicks; Mary Hicks; Bessie Proffitt; Unidentified (small boy); Rosa Hicks (wearing white dress); Unidentified taller boy; Rena Hicks, holding baby Roger Hicks; Nell Hicks (small girl in front of Rena); Anna Hicks (in front); Willis Hicks; Unidentified (boy with hat). (Box 28, Print 2A: 1)
        - Bessie Proffitt (on porch), Rena Hicks, Anne Warner. (Box 28, Print 2A: 2)
        - Boone Court house. (Box 28, Print 2A: 3)
        - Rena Hicks (left, in back), holding baby Roger Hicks; Oliver Proffitt (standing in front of girl in chair); Others unidentified. (Box 28, Print 2A: 4)
        - Mary and Lewis Hicks. (Box 28, Print 2A: 5)
        - Boone County Court house. (Box 28, Print 2A: 6)
      - 2B (14) Hicks porch gathering, Beech Mountain, N.C.
        - Rena Hicks (left, in back), holding baby Roger Hicks); Oliver Proffitt (standing in front of girl in chair); others unidentified. (Box 28, Print 2B: 1)
        - Ben Hicks, Frank Warner, Frank Proffitt, Nathan Hicks, Roby Monroe Hicks (crouching, wearing hat). (Box 28, Print 2B: 2)
        - Hicks family (and others): Rena Hicks (far left), holding baby Roger Hicks; Lewis and Mary Hicks (standing together, right of center, Mary wearing white shirt over dress); others unidentified. (Box 28, Print 2B: 3)
        - Ben Hicks, Frank Warner, Nathan Hicks, Roby Monroe Hicks (crouching, wearing hat). (Box 28, Print 2B: 4)
        - Ben Hicks, Frank Warner, Nathan Hicks, Roby Monroe Hicks (crouching, wearing hat.) (Box 28, Print 2B: 5)
        - Ben Hicks with two unidentified girls. (Box 28, Print 2B: 6)
        - (A long distance photo; none really identifiable.) (Box 28, Print 2B: 7)
        - Four unidentified singing girls. Behind them: Frank and Bessie Proffitt. (Box 28, Print 2B: 8)
        - Roby Monroe Hicks. (Box 28, Print 2B: 9)
        - Ben Hicks, four unidentified singing girls. Behind them: Frank and Bessie Proffitt, and unidentified woman. (Box 28, Print 2B: 10)
        - Several unidentified children, Anne Warner (standing off of the porch, right of center). In back: Bessie Proffitt; Rosa Hicks (standing in doorway); Rena Hicks, holding baby Roger Hicks; Unidentified (woman wearing white dress); Ray Hicks; Lewis Hicks; Unidentified (man in overalls, far right). (Box 28, Print 2B: 11)
        - Lewis and Mary Hicks with baby Roger Hicks. (Box 28, Print 2B: 12)
        - Home of Nathan and Rena Hicks. (Box 28, Print 2B: 13)
        - In back: Anna Hicks, holding Jack Hicks; Willis Hicks (in front), holding unidentified child; Nell Hicks (just right of center, hands over mouth), two unidentified girls (flanking either side). (Box 28, Print 2B: 14)
    - Lot 3: 1939
      - 3A (12) Adirondacks, N.Y..
        - Anne Warner with unidentified woman and dog at Log House. (Box 28, Print 3A: 1)
        - Anne Warner (wearing stripe Jacket) with Morris and Irene Bennett (other adults). The three Bennett children pictured here are otherwise unidentifiable. Rome, N.Y. (Box 28, Print 3A: 2)
        - Frank Warner with a group of unidentified people. (Box 28, Print 3A: 3)
        - Aiden Lair, a country inn, northwest of Minerva, N.Y. (Box 28, Print 3A: 4)
        - Bennett cottage, unidentified man. (Box 28, Print 3A: 5)
        - Silver Bay, N.Y. (a YMCA resort and a favorite retreat of the Warners). (Box 28, Print 3A: 6)
        - Aiden Lair. Anne Warner (wearing stripe jacket) with unidentified woman and dogs. (Box 28, Print 3A: 7)
        - Frank Warner and (Yankee) John Galusha. (Box 28, Print 3A: 8)
        - Unidentified. (Box 28, Print 3A: 9)
        - Aiden Lair. (Box 28, Print 3A: 10)
        - (Yankee) John Galusha. (Box 28, Print 3A: 11)
        - Anne and Frank Warner (standing in back), (Yankee) John Galusha (seated). (Box 28, Print 3A: 12)
      - 3B (13) Beech Mountain, N.C.
        - Rena, Nathan, and Nell (little girl in front) Hicks. (Box 28, Print 3B: 1)
        - Ray Hicks with groundhog. (Box 28, Print 3B: 2)
        - Buna and Roby Monroe Hicks. (Box 28, Print 3B: 3)
        - Some of the Hicks family: Ray; Willis, holding Jack; Mary, holding Roger; Nathan; Rena; Nell; Anna; N.A.; Lewis. (Box 28, Print 3B: 4)
        - Two unidentified boys, Frank Proffitt, Roby Monroe Hicks (back to camera), Frank Warner, Nathan Hicks, Sam Hicks, Vance Presnell (leaning forward, legs crossed), Linzy Hicks (wearing hat), and Ray Hicks (lying down). (Box 28, Print 3B: 5)
        - Home of Nathan and Rena Hicks. (Box 28, Print 3B: 6)
        - Anna Hicks. (Box 28, Print 3B: 7)
        - Buna and Roby Monroe Hicks. (Box 28, Print 3B: 8)
        - Willis Hicks and baby Roger Hicks. (Box 28, Print 3B: 9)
        - Nathan Hicks. (Box 28, Print 3B: 10)
        - Nathan Hicks. (Box 28, Print 3B: 11)
        - Buna and Roby Monroe Hicks. (Box 28, Print 3B: 12)
        - Home of Roby Monroe Hicks and Buna Hicks at Beech Creek, N.C. (Box 28, Print 3B: 13)
    - Lot 4: 1940
      - 4A (15) Beech Mountain, N.C., Hicks porch gathering.
        - Nathan Hicks, Roby Monroe Hicks (in back, head down), Ray Hicks (in back), Frank Proffitt, Linzy Hicks. (Box 28, Print 4A: 1)
        - Back: Willis Hicks, holding unidentified child; Nathan Hicks; Roby Monroe Hicks; Ray Hicks; Frank Proffitt; Linzy Hicks. Front: Oliver Proffitt; Nell Hicks; Bessie Proffitt; Rena Hicks; Rosa Hicks; Anna Hicks, holding unidentified infant; and Mary Hicks. (Box 28, Print 4A: 2)
        - Back: Willis Hicks, holding unidentified child; Nathan Hicks; Roby Monroe Hicks; Ray Hicks; Frank Proffitt; Linzy Hicks. Front: Oliver Proffitt; Nell Hicks; Bessie Proffitt; Rena Hicks; Rosa Hicks; Anna Hicks, holding unidentified infant; and Mary Hicks. (Box 28, Print 4A: 3)
        - Unidentified child, Nathan Hicks, and Roby Monroe Hicks. (Box 28, Print 4A: 4)
        - Nell Hicks (seated bottom left), Anne Warner (seated, next to Nell), Unidentified man (leaning on post), Anna Hicks (standing behind Anne Warner), Unidentified man (seated in chair on porch), Oliver Proffitt (older boy, seated on porch, center), Unidentified (smaller boy), Ray Hicks (seated, right of center, next to post), N.A. Hicks, Linzy Hicks, and two unidentified men (bottom right, crouching). (Box 28, Print 4A: 5)
        - Back: all unidentified. Front: Frank Proffitt, Nathan Hicks, Unidentified, Unidentified, Rena Hicks, Linzy Hicks, Unidentified, N.A. Hicks, Ray Hicks, and Lewis Hicks. (Box 28, Print 4A: 6)
        - Unidentified child, Nathan Hicks, and Roby Monroe Hicks. (Box 28, Print 4A: 7)
        - Nathan Hicks, Roby Monroe Hicks, Frank Proffitt, Ray Hicks, and Linzy Hicks. (Box 28, Print 4A: 8)
        - Willis Hicks (in back), Unidentified child, Nathan Hicks, Roby Monroe Hicks. (Box 28, Print 4A: 9)
        - Bessie Hicks, Rosa Hicks, Nell Hicks (seated on porch), both men unidentified. (Box 28, Print 4A: 10)
        - Anna Hicks. (Box 28, Print 4A: 11)
        - N.A. Hicks, Willis Hicks, Roby Monroe Hicks, Ray Hicks (in back, next to Roby), Frank Proffitt, Linzy Hicks, Frank Warner, Oliver Proffitt. (Box 28, Print 4A: 12)
        - Rosa Hicks, Anna Hicks, Anne Warner, Rena Hicks, Bessie Proffitt. (Box 28, Print 4A: 13)
        - Ray Hicks. (Box 28, Print 4A: 14)
        - Frank Proffitt, Nathan Hicks, N.A. Hicks, Linzy Hicks, Nell Hicks, Anne Warner (in back, stripe jacket), Rena Hicks, and Anna Hicks. (Box 28, Print 4A: 15)
      - 4B (21) Northern Trip.
        - Louis Solomon ( St. Regis Reservation, N.Y.) (Box 28, Print 4B: 1)
        - Walter Mallory's house in Dorset, V.T. Unidentified, Anne Warner, Unidentified. (Box 28, Print 4B: 2)
        - Happy Lynch and Anne Warner at Walter Mallory's House in Dorset, V.T. (Box 28, Print 4B: 3)
        - St. Mary's Church in Irishtown, N.Y. (Box 28, Print 4B: 4)
        - Two Mohawk women and Louis Solomon at the St. Regis Indian Reservation, N.Y. (Box 28, Print 4B: 5)
        - Stone House Inn in N.H. Anne Warner in car. (Box 28, Print 4B: 6)
        - Happy Lynch. (Box 28, Print 4B: 7)
        - Log House, all unidentified. (Box 28, Print 4B: 8)
        - Anne Warner at a cottage in which the Warners stayed at Saranac Lake in the Adirondacks, N.Y.. (Box 28, Print 4B: 9)
        - At Log House, all unidentified. (Box 28, Print 4B: 10)
        - St. Regis Indian Reservation, N.Y.: Anne Warner (second from left, wearing stripe jacket) and Louis Solomon (man seated between other two, wearing suspenders), others unidentified. (Box 28, Print 4B: 11)
        - Frank Warner with Happy Lynch. (Box 28, Print 4B: 12)
        - Mrs. Murphy ( Hogansberg, N.Y.). (Box 28, Print 4B: 13)
        - Louis Solomon and Frank Warner. (Box 28, Print 4B: 14)
        - Louis Solomon (center) and two young Mohawk men at the St. Regis Reservation, N.Y. (Box 28, Print 4B: 15)
        - Anne Warner (front left) and unidentified woman (behind Warner) with Louis Solomon (center, wearing suspenders) and two Mohawk men (otherwise unidentified) at St. Regis Reservation, N.Y. (Box 28, Print 4B: 16)
        - MacDowell Colony in N.H.: Unidentified, Betty and Carl Carmer, Marjorie Flock, Bill Benet, Anne Warner, and Dorothy Heywood. (Box 28, Print 4B: 17)
        - Happy Lynch. (Box 28, Print 4B: 18)
        - A sailing trip from Marblehead. Unidentified. (Box 28, Print 4B: 19)
        - Frank Warner at cottage on Lake Saranac in the Adirondacks, N.Y. (Box 28, Print 4B: 20)
        - Anne Warner and unidentified woman with Louis Solomon and two otherwise unidentified Mohawk men at the St. Regis Mohawk Indian Reservation, N.Y. (Box 28, Print 4B: 21)
      - 4C (6) Northeast.
        - Lena Bourne Fish using the Warners' Wilcox Gay Recordio in her home in East Jaffrey, N.H. (Box 28, Print 4C: 1)
        - Lena Bourne Fish at her home in East Jaffrey, N.H. (Box 28, Print 4C: 2)
        - (Yankee) John Galusha at his home in Minerva, N.Y. (Box 28, Print 4C: 3)
        - Lena Bourne Fish in her home in East Jaffrey, N.H. (Box 28, Print 4C: 4)
        - Lena Bourne Fish with kitten at her home in East Jaffrey, N.H. (Box 28, Print 4C: 5)
        - (Yankee) John Galusha and Anne Warner at a distance at Galusha's home in Minerva, N.Y. (Box 28, Print 4C: 6)
      - 4D (10) Southeastern Trip.
        - Rebecca King Jones' home in Crab Tree Creek, N.C.: Unidentified, Anne Warner, and Rebecca King Jones. (Box 28, Print 4D: 1)
        - Charles K. (Tink), Cliff, Eleazar, and Hub Tillett with dog in Wanchese, N.C. (Box 28, Print 4D: 2)
        - Rebecca King Jones. (Box 28, Print 4D: 3)
        - Bill Moss and Jesse McDonald in Suffolk, Va. (Box 28, Print 4D: 4)
        - Home of Captain John and Alwilda Culpeper at Nag's Head, N.C. (Box 28, Print 4D: 5)
        - Unidentified and Steve Meekins. Kitty Hawk, N.C. (Box 28, Print 4D: 6)
        - Aunt Armise Spruille (standing), Bill Moss (holding microphone), Joseph Henry (Uncle Joe) Johnson, and Jesse McDonald. Suffolk, Va. (Box 28, Print 4D: 7)
        - Frank Warner, Rebecca King Jones, and Anne Warner at the Warners' house in Durham, N.C. (Box 28, Print 4D: 8)
        - Rebecca King Jones' home in Crab Tree Creek, N.C.: Unidentified, Anne Warner (seated on floor), Rebecca King Jones, unidentified, and the otherwise unidentified soldiers. (Box 28, Print 4D: 9)
        - Anne Warner and Charles K. (Tink) Tillett with Lemon (pony). Roanoke Island, N.C. (Box 28, Print 4D: 10)
        - Mr. and Mrs. Tillett with son and nephew. Wanchese, N.C., 1940 (Box 28, Print 4D: 11)
    - Lot 5: 1941-1942
      - 5A (4) Southeast.
        - Anne Warner, Verdon Thomas (standing), Sue Thomas, J.B. Sutton. Elizabeth City, N.C. (Box 28, Print 5A: 1)
        - Anne Warner, Verdon Thomas (standing), Sue Thomas, J.B. Sutton. Elizabeth City, N.C. (Box 28, Print 5A: 2)
        - Captain John and Alwilda Culpeper. Nag's Head, N.C. (Box 28, Print 5A: 3)
        - Frank Warner with Alwilda and Captain John Culpeper on the porch of the Culpeper's home at Nag's Head, N.C. (Box 28, Print 5A: 4)
      - 5B (17) Beech Mountain, N.C.
        - Frank, Bessie, and Oliver Proffitt on the steps of their first house in Pick Britches Valley, Watuga County, N.C. (Box 28, Print 5B: 1)
        - Frank Proffitt (back, standing), Nancy Prather (in front of Frank), Bessie Proffitt (next to Nancy), Oliver Proffitt (front row, middle), and 8 otherwise unidentified Proffitt relations. Pick Britches Valley, N.C. (Box 28, Print 5B: 2)
        - Mary Hicks (in back), Rena Hicks, and Anne Warner. (Box 28, Print 5B: 3)
        - Anne Warner, Frank Proffitt, and three unidentified children. Pick Britches Valley, N.C. (Box 28, Print 5B: 4)
        - Nell and Rena Hicks. (Box 28, Print 5B: 5)
        - Dewey, Linzy, Buna, Roby Monroe, and Rosa Hicks. (Box 28, Print 5B: 6)
        - The Hicks' wintergreen still. Linzy (with guitar), Nathan, two unidentified (with hats, right of center), and Lewis Hicks. (Box 28, Print 5B: 7)
        - The Proffitts' first house in Pick Britches Valley, N.C. Anne Warner and Frank Proffitt (in front). Others unidentified. (Box 28, Print 5B: 8)